<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ojasyearlypredictions>
  <aries>
    <general>For Arians, 2014 is going to be a good year. Horoscope 2014 astrology predicts that family life will be happy. However, Saturn and Rahu are in 7th house. It may create some difference of opinion with your spouse in 2014. Also, it may give health troubles to your partner, as per the predictions made by 2014 horoscope. When it comes to health, 2014 astrology predicts that you might see some ups and downs. Therefore, you should stay cautious to avoid diseases. Also, it's a good time for love-life. But, not a good time for inter-caste relationships. So, beware of your actions if the love of your life is not your caste. On professional front, this year may bring you promotion. Horoscope 2014 predictions say that you will witness a positive time financially. If you want to go for higher education, you may get very favorable results. Students who are planning to go abroad for further studies, time seems quite favorable after June, 2014. Serve black cows as a remedial measure.</general>
  </aries>
  <taurus>
    <general>2014 is full of surprises for Taureans. As per your astrology for 2014 horoscope, you may think something special for your loved ones. It will enhance your reputation, according to your 2014 astrology. If you are not already suffering from some old disease, health-wise this year is going to be good for you. Even if you are suffering through an old disease, improvement can be expected. It's also a good time for love-life, albeit there might be some minor differences. 2014 predictions suggest that it would be better if you can avoid any argument. It's a positive period for career, according to the predictions made by 2014 horoscope. Those who're jobless may get job, however businesspersons need more hard-work, because you will not be able to fetch much positive results without putting your endeavor. If you have worked hard, most of your efforts will be successful. Financially, 2014 is favorable for you. As per the horoscope 2014, there are good chances of saving money in the first half of the year. On the other hand, second half of the year may bring increment in income. Students will reap beneficial results, according to the predictions made by 2014 astrology. As a remedial measure, serve girls to improve 2014 even more.</general>
  </taurus>
  <gemini>
    <general>Predictions of 2014 horoscope tell about those who belong to Gemini that the year is going to be favorable. There may be some important function in your family in 2014. Also, there are good chances of a wedding or newborn at home. However, keep an eye on your health. Though you may not face any major illness, but seasonal diseases may trouble you at times. 2014 predictions suggest you to not be stubborn in matters related to love. Otherwise, your love partner may get attracted to someone else. As per your 2014 astrology, you might feel attracted to someone socially different from you. It is a good time for business and job. You will get relief from unemployment or may get a promotion. Also, it is a positive period financially. According to 2014 horoscope, your income sources may increase. Try to stay away from risky investments. For students, 2014 is good enough. Time is exclusively special for higher studies, as per horoscope 2014. Donate almonds in a temple to improve your prospects this year.</general>
  </gemini>
  <cancer>
    <general>Cancerians, 2014 is going to give you mixed results. As per 2014 horoscope, you may have to face some problems in first half of the year. Rahu and Saturn in fourth house may disturb your mental peace. Horoscopes for 2014 astrology predicts that you may stay stressed due to domestic life. In 2014, you might not gel well with your family members. It will give you stress. This time isn't favorable for health, job, education and traveling. In such situation, you will have to stay alert for your health all the time. Horoscope 2014 astrology has predicted that the transition is also expected in your job. Avoid any useless argument with your seniors; also avoid unimportant travels. However, the second half would prove to be much better. By and by, your troubles will wane. 2014 predictions say that religious and spiritual activities would bring you peace. In the second half of the year, level of your education will improve and all your endeavors for higher education will be successful. Feed a cow with rice mixed with milk to ward off your troubles.</general>
  </cancer>
  <leo>
    <general>Lions, you are going to get various favorable results in first half of the year. 2014 horoscope predicts that your family members will be happy in the first half of the year. Income sources will improve in 2014. You will get immense support from friends and relatives. As per 2014 astrology predictions, time is also favorable for progeny and education. However, the aspect of Saturn in fifth house may give you progeny related tensions; however, all the issues will keep on resolving with time. Health-wise, it's a good time. As per 2014 astrology, it's also a positive period for love affairs and progeny. Horoscopes 2014 says that many beneficial opportunities might come your way. As per your 2014 astrology, you will do well on professional front. Chances of promotion are also seen in 2014. Students may succeed in cracking desired entrance exams. However, spending may increase during second half. Also, this period isn't that positive from health's point-of-view. You may have to go on some useless journeys. Water the Peepal tree as a remedial measure.</general>
  </leo>
  <virgo>
    <general>Overall, 2014 is a beneficial year for you. In 2014, there will be a positive environment at home. You'll remain healthy and happy. However, I would like to suggest you to keep a control over your tongue. Additionally, you need to avoid unnecessary expenditures. Especially, the second half is better for love affairs and marriage. According to the horoscope 2014, you may do something extraordinary in your profession. Promotion is also possible. You may get more opportunities in 2014. However, Saturn and Rahu are in second house. Therefore, you'll find it a bit difficult to save the money. However, the Rahu's transit in July may help you in savings and this transit is also good for your health. 2014 astrology predicts that students may get favorable results. Apply saffron Tilak on your forehead to make things positive for you. </general>
  </virgo>
  <libra>
    <general>You can expect mixed results from 2014. If you're spiritual in nature, you will be able to create harmonious environment in your family because Jupiter in your ninth house is strengthening your good luck. Saturn and Rahu in your first house may cause some troubles to your health. However, in July, after Rahu transit, health related issues will be resolved. This is a good year for matters related to love. However, there might be some issues in your married life. 2014 horoscope suggests you to avoid not-so-important lawsuits, it will lead you to wastage of time and money. You might also face problems on professional front in 2014. But, you will get success in some matters even after hurdles. Financially, 2014 is an average year. Students may get favorable results, if they put in hard work. Time is positive for those who want to take education abroad. As remedial measures, serve monkeys. Also, avoid non-vegetarian food and alcohol. </general>
  </libra>
  <scorpio>
    <general>According to your 2014 astrology, Jupiter is situated in your eighth house in the beginning of the year. During initial phase of 2014, you need to work hard to get some favorable results. 2014 horoscope foretells that family members might behave strangely. Be careful as a feeling of insecurity may affect your health. Your 2014 horoscope suggests you to avoid lawsuits as much as possible. Unnecessary travels are also not good for you. There might be some discord in love affairs too. Even toiling wouldn't yield expected results. However, second half of 2014 is going to bring improvement because Jupiter will be in your ninth house during that phase. Rahu will reach your eleventh house in July. This transit will bring improvements for you. As a result, students will get good results; and your earning may soar up too. Donation of Ghee along with potatoes will be beneficial for you. </general>
  </scorpio>
  <saggittarius>
    <general>The first part of 2014 is going to be very good for you. Your 2014 astrology predictions foretells that things would be harmonious in family. You'll feel yourself rejuvenated. Saturn and Rahu posited in your eleventh house are indicating increments for you. But, Saturn's effect over ascendant house may empower some negativities in you. Hence, your efforts should be concentrated on avoiding any negative act and bad habits. Your 2014 horoscope predicts that you may get expected results in matters related to love and marriage. However, Saturn's effect in fifth house may cause some arguments with your love partner at times. It would be great if you can avoid arguments on small issues. It's a positive period professionally. Students would get the results of their hard work. However, you might face some problems in every sphere of your life during second half. As per 2014 predictions, it'd be prudent to invest carefully. Stay at bay from the greed of making quick money. Working people need to stay very careful. You may have to change your job or may get transferred to an unwanted destination. Float coconuts in flowing water every four months to improve the things.</general>
  </saggittarius>
  <capricorn>
    <general>2014 has mixed results for you. Jupiter is transiting to your fifth house in the starting of this month. Ups and downs can be seen in financial matters. You may have to pay special attention to the matters related to debts. Your horoscope 2014 astrology says there might be some difference of opinion with family members. Also, health may not be that good. However, diseases will not trouble you much. There are slight chances of some differences or court cases too. But this time may give you victory in lawsuits, be it after troubles. Your enemies may trouble you to some extent, but victory will be yours at the end. You may see improvement in love affairs during the second half. Marriage might bring happiness. Any auspicious event may be organized at your home. If you are into partnership, you will be benefited. Earnings and knowledge, both will improve according to 2014 horoscopes. Donating yellow colored clothes to a priest would prove to be beneficial for you. </general>
  </capricorn>
  <aquarius>
    <general>You're going to have a brilliant start of 2014. Some auspicious festivals may take place in your family. It would be a great time for family planning. This time duration could be said very auspicious for education too. Journeys to distant places will prove to be beneficial, as per your horoscope 2014. Especially for spiritual journeys, the time is good. You'll enjoy good health; however it is a must to keep a check on your diet. Be careful while driving. You may get a better job. Stars indicate toward soaring profits. Education-wise it is a good time. However, you might face some hurdles in second half. Some people may start standing against you without any reason. Some issues related to the exchange of debts may also sprout up as per astrology for 2014. It would be great if you can avoid making any significant investment. If you are planning a journey via water route, then try to avoid it as much as you can. Donate rice, jaggery and gram in a temple to ward off negative effects of stars.</general>
  </aquarius>
  <pisces>
    <general>Year 2014 will prove to be quite beneficial for you. Even though you are affected by Dhaiyya of Saturn, but Jupiter's blessings will stay with you. There will be harmony at home. You'll enjoy good health. Time will also stay good to buy a new home or vehicle. According to your predictions for 2014 horoscope, the second half would prove to be good for marriage and love affairs. But, after July, Rahu is transiting to your seventh house, which may cause stress in marital life. You may spend some money for the growth of your own business as per 2014 astrology. Seniors are going to be helpful for you. You may commence something new while executing your plans. Stars indicate toward improved income. But if you are working into partnership, then I would suggest you to stay careful. For students, this time is quite beneficial according to horoscope of 2014. But, the time is more positive for those who are planning to go for higher studies.</general>
  </pisces>
</ojasyearlypredictions>
